<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Responsive on Hugo中文文档</title>
    <link>https://www.gohugo.org/tags/responsive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Responsive on Hugo中文文档</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.coderzh.com/&#34;&gt;CoderZh&lt;/a&gt; 2015.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gohugo.org/tags/responsive/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-h5bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-h5bp/</guid>
      <description>hugo-h5bp-simple Simple responsive theme for Go Hugo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-icarus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-icarus/</guid>
      <description>Icarus Icarus is a responsive and customizable theme for bloggers. It&amp;rsquo;s a port of the same-named theme for Hexo made by Ruipeng Zhang. Noteworthy features of this Hugo theme are the integration of a comment-system powered by Disqus, localization (l10n) support, syntax highlighting for source code, optional widgets for the sidebar and a handful shortcodes to make your life easier.
Get the theme I assume you&amp;rsquo;ve Git installed. Inside the folder of your Hugo site run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-minimalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-minimalist/</guid>
      <description>Minimalist Minimalist is a responsive theme with a focus on blogging based on the Minimalistic Ghost theme made by Raphael Riegger . Noteworthy features of this Hugo theme are the integration of a comment-system powered by Disqus, easy localization (l10n), support for RSS feeds, syntax highlighting for source code and sharing options in the blog posts.

Contents  Installation The config file Localization (l10n) Nearly finished Contributing License Annotations  Installation Inside the folder of your Hugo site run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-uno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugo-uno/</guid>
      <description>hugo-uno A responsive hugo theme with awesome font&amp;rsquo;s, charts and light-box galleries, the theme is based on Uno for ghost. A example site is available at fredrikloch.me
A Swedish translation is available in the branch feature/swedish
Usage The following is a short tutorial on the usage of some features in the theme.
Configuration To take full advantage of the features in this theme you can add variables to your site config file, the following is the example config from the example site:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugoscroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/hugoscroll/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Scroll A live example of this theme is running at this site hugoscroll.fredrikloch.me
Using scroll To get started with hugo you first need to download the binaries, whith these in place it is easy to get started.
# Init site hugo new site My_New_Cool_Venture cd My_New_Cool_Venture # Get this cool theme git clone https://github.com/SenjinDarashiva/hugoscroll themes/hugoscroll # Start the watching your folder hugo --buildDrafts --theme=&amp;quot;hugoscroll&amp;quot; --watch server  With this done you can start creating posts, for this theme theme there is some specific information that needs to be added to your post header.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/tinyce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/tinyce/</guid>
      <description>Tinyce Tinyce is a general-purpose Hugo theme.
You can check the live version here.
Getting started Once you have Hugo up and running, you must:
Create a Hugo project:
$ hugo new site my-site  And then install tinyce:
$ cd themes $ git clone https://github.com/roperzh/tinyce-hugo-theme  If you are using Hugo v0.11 or below, please read this
Now you can set tinyce as the default theme for your site by adding this line in the config file:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>