<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contact Form on Hugo中文文档</title>
    <link>https://www.gohugo.org/tags/contact-form/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contact Form on Hugo中文文档</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.coderzh.com/&#34;&gt;CoderZh&lt;/a&gt; 2015.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gohugo.org/tags/contact-form/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/agency/</guid>
      <description>Agency Theme Agency Theme is a one page portfolio for companies and freelancers based on the original Bootstrap theme by David Miller. This Hugo theme features several content sections, a responsive portfolio grid with hover effects, full page portfolio item modals, a timeline, and a contact form.
Contents  Installation Getting started  The config file Change the hero background Present your skills Create your portfolio Show what happened Introduce your team List your clients Make the contact form working Nearly finished  Contributing License Annotations  Installation Inside the folder of your Hugo site run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/artists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/artists/</guid>
      <description>Artists Theme The Artists Theme is a one page portfolio for freelancers based on the original Jekyll theme by Travis Neilson aka DevTips and his many contributors. It&amp;rsquo;s the result of a longer video series made by him that is showing the whole developement process from the first designs to the final Jekyll theme. Consider to subscribe to his YouTube channel.
This Hugo theme features several content sections, like an about section showing the level of your skills, a responsive portfolio with hover effects, a gallery to present your client&amp;rsquo;s opinions and a contact form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/strata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/strata/</guid>
      <description>Strata Theme The Strata theme is a responsive and minimal one-page-portfolio based on the self-named template made by HTML5UP. Noteworthy features of this Hugo theme are a custom about section, a portfolio with gallery for photographs or client works and a contact form.
Contents  Installation Getting started  The config file Sidebar Build up your portfolio Make the contact form working Nearly finished  Contributing License Annotations  Installation Inside the folder of your Hugo site run:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>