<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost on Hugo中文文档</title>
    <link>https://www.gohugo.org/tags/ghost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ghost on Hugo中文文档</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.coderzh.com/&#34;&gt;CoderZh&lt;/a&gt; 2015.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gohugo.org/tags/ghost/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/crisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/crisp/</guid>
      <description>Crisp A minimalist, responsive, and open-source theme for Hugo by Kathy Qian.
Editing Follow Buttons Crisp uses Font Awesome for icons. See the Font Awesome documentation for the full list of icons and usage tips.
I have placed some common buttons in follow.hbs, with more options in the commented out sections. Make sure to replace the username in the URLs so the links point to your profiles.
Features, Changelog, and Technical Notes Please see the wiki for details regarding previous releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/detox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/detox/</guid>
      <description>Detox Detox is a beautiful theme, originally created to work with Ghost. I wanted a copy of this theme for use with Hugo.
The original can be downloaded from Blueberry.
License MIT License</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/steam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gohugo.org/theme/steam/</guid>
      <description>Steam Steam is a minimal and customizable theme for bloggers and was developed by Tommaso Barbato. He created it as a slightly adapted version of the Vapor Ghost theme by Seth Lilly. Noteworthy features of this Hugo port are the integration of a comment-system either powered by Disqus or Google Plus, the customizable appearance by changing theme colors, support for RSS feeds, syntax highlighting for source code and the optional use of Google Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>